<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
    xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
    <ui:style>
    
    </ui:style>
    <g:HTMLPanel>
        <p>Choose a Vograbulary challenge.</p>
        <dl>
            <dt><a href="#ultraghost">Ultraghost</a></dt>
            <dd>On each turn, you are given a three letter puzzle, like CIP. You
                have to find a word that starts with the first letter, contains
                the middle letter, and ends with the last letter. For example,
                CRISP starts with C, contains I, and ends with P. Once you enter
                your answer, your opponent has a few seconds to enter a better
                one. An answer is better if it is shorter, or if it is the same
                length and comes earlier in the dictionary. For example CLIP is
                shorter than CRISP. The app will then give you a hint if there
                are any better words that you didn't think of. For example,
                CHIP is earlier than CLIP in the dictionary.</dd>
            <dt><a href="#hyperghost">Hyperghost</a></dt>
            <dd>Very similar to Hyperghost, but you reuse the same letters until
                no one can think of another word. Each new word has to be
                slightly worse than the previous word. The other students can
                respond with a word that is between the two words. If the
                Ultraghost example above were in Hyperghost, the next student
                would have to find another word for CIP that is longer or later
                than CRISP, such as COWSLIP.</dd>
            <dt><a href="#russian">Russian Dolls</a></dt>
            <dd>Find the secret word described by a clue. One of the words from
                the clue is nested inside another to form the secret word.</dd>
            <dt><a href="#students">Students</a></dt>
            <dd>Edit student names.</dd>
        </dl>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 